<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>btaars.net on btaars.net</title>
    <link>http://blog.btaars.net/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content in btaars.net on btaars.net</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 May 2017 00:05:08 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Painful love</title>
      <link>http://blog.btaars.net/post/painful-love/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2017 00:05:08 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.btaars.net/post/painful-love/</guid>
      <description>i love you so much, it hurts sometimes
i think so much about you, i forget to breath sometimes
i am so full of love for you, but feel so lonely sometimes
i feel disoriented, lost and alone in this world
i want you so bad, to bring you to my world
i want so bad our worlds to merge
help me, help me please, help me be better
help me babe become sane and clean</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creating this blog with Hugo &amp; Github Pages</title>
      <link>http://blog.btaars.net/post/creating-this-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2017 00:14:07 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.btaars.net/post/creating-this-blog/</guid>
      <description>I had time during the new year holidays, so I went online to look for a web framework to develop web applications in golang. I accidently lended on the hugo site and discovered this awesome tool. The concept is very simple: you can easily generate a static website in a few minutes. This was quite different from what I was looking for, but it looked interesting and I decided to give it a try.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello World!</title>
      <link>http://blog.btaars.net/post/first/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2017 20:06:19 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.btaars.net/post/first/</guid>
      <description>$ printf &amp;quot;%s\n&amp;quot; &#39;Hello, World!&#39; Hello, World!  I&amp;rsquo;m starting a fresh blog site and this is my first post. I&amp;rsquo;ll try my best to post frequently and keep the site alive. A brief introduction I&amp;rsquo;ve been living in Japan for a very long time. I currently work in a Japanese company (been working there for more than a decade now). In the beginning, I&amp;rsquo;ve had the chance to work as a technical support staff for one year.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
