<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on btaars.net</title>
    <link>https://blog.btaars.net/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on btaars.net</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Mar 2018 00:14:07 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/post/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Introducing petitdb</title>
      <link>https://blog.btaars.net/post/introducing-petitdb/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Mar 2018 00:14:07 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.btaars.net/post/introducing-petitdb/</guid>
      <description>What is petitdb petitdb is a python library that I created a few years ago. As you can guess by the name, it&amp;rsquo;s a library that provides some basic database functionnalities. Under the hood it&amp;rsquo;s just operating on shelves, inside which dicts of dicts are created. Each dict in the shelve is presented as a table, and inside each dict resides another dict that stores key/value pairs.
Use cases One way I used this library was to store some configurations, mainly hostnames and some others attributes that go with it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About logs</title>
      <link>https://blog.btaars.net/post/about_logging/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2017 01:23:06 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.btaars.net/post/about_logging/</guid>
      <description>I was looking for an article online that explains clearly how to idiomatically do logging in golang. What is the best practice? This is the article that I found by googling golang logging. It turned out not to be how-to article, but rather an opinion about what should developers log when writing their applications. Here are some thoughts about the article. I agree with some of the author&amp;rsquo;s opinions while I don&amp;rsquo;t with others.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creating this blog with Hugo &amp; Github Pages</title>
      <link>https://blog.btaars.net/post/creating-this-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2017 00:14:07 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.btaars.net/post/creating-this-blog/</guid>
      <description>I had time during the new year holidays, so I went online to look for a web framework to develop web applications in golang. I accidently lended on the hugo site and discovered this awesome tool. The concept is very simple: you can easily generate a static website in a few minutes. This was quite different from what I was looking for, but it looked interesting and I decided to give it a try.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello World!</title>
      <link>https://blog.btaars.net/post/first/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2017 20:06:19 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.btaars.net/post/first/</guid>
      <description>$ printf &amp;quot;%s\n&amp;quot; &#39;Hello, World!&#39; Hello, World!  I&amp;rsquo;m starting a fresh blog site and this is my first post. I&amp;rsquo;ll try my best to post frequently and keep the site alive. A brief introduction I&amp;rsquo;ve been living in Japan for a very long time. I currently work in a Japanese company (been working there for more than a decade now). In the beginning, I&amp;rsquo;ve had the chance to work as a technical support staff for one year.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
